The world knows you as a fighter. Like
you're an incredible fighter,
entertaining fighter, feisty fighter,
wrestling, all of it. But content
creation, I don't know if anybody's
creating better content than you today.
>> You got to take it and do it by
yourself. If you fail,
>> stand up and go try it again.
>> You're the one fight nobody wants,
right? You're the guy that everybody
wants to delay.
>> This sport is getting big because of
drama, not because of fighting. like uh
Connor Habib Diaz.
>> What's the next big one for you? Body,
don't say that. Are you serious?
>> They send me contract. I sign and give
it back.
>> Take the fight against Ilia 4. You take
it. Don't pay me nothing.
>> It's okay. I'll fight for you. USA.
>> Fight for you.
>> And uh I look forward to the day we
celebrate as the first Armenian UFC
champion.
>> Yeah. So when I get the belt, I flew out
here and put the belt on this table and
we talk again.
>> 100%.
Arman Sarukan, how are you?
>> Great, thank you. How are you?
>> Very good. Do we want to do this hyenic
ang
on English? If I don't understand, I'm
going to start to do.
>> So, it's it's my first time when someone
knows Armenian and English. So,
>> so for me, I'm going to be both a
translator and the interviewer, which is
going to be good.
>> Yeah. I always have my friend. He's
sitting and listening the old podcast.
If I don't understand question, I al
always ask him. And now I said, "Bro,
today you can leave because
>> you don't need the translation."
>> Yeah. If I don't understand something,
I'll I'll let you know.
>> I got to tell you, I I messaged you.
What was it? Two months ago, three
months ago. I said, "Brother, what are
you doing with all this content?" Of
course, the world knows you as a
fighter. Like, you're an incredible
fighter, entertaining fighter, feisty
fighter, wrestling, all of it. But
content creation, I don't know if
anybody's creating better content than
you today. How did that happen?
>> It's it's come natural, you know. Um I
have a good lifestyle.
I can afford fly private jet yachts and
I I love that lifestyle and people love
it too. So the nice cars when I posted
like a food and um so I post maybe three
years ago when I was eating in and out
>> and it went viral. I had maybe like 300
or 400,000 followers and it was like 6 7
millions and I said, "Okay, uh maybe
people like because I fought versus D is
Gulov. I beat him. I got I gained like a
40,000
40,000 likes for the for the winning
>> right after the fight.
>> Yeah. But when I post the In and Out, I
got 250,000 likes. I said, "Why I beat
this guy?" Like, and I didn't go viral
and I just post the burgers and uh I
went viral. So, and I decided like to do
something more with my social media. But
like last half, last six months, we just
crush it and like non-stop working. And
uh you know, I don't push myself. It's
like come natural and uh it's easy for
me. So people think I I have a like a
big team like we just create something
crazy every day thinking about like a uh
reals what are we going to post this
that it's like every every post almost
every real is it's like almost my my um
my lifestyle you know we don't we just
create by all organic just kind
>> yeah we don't think even like Ashen Hall
he came to me and say bro what are we
going to do I said we're going to train
do something and they just we just
create from there
>> because if we going to think and sit
>> it's not going to be natural. So come,
we we wrestle, we box, we run, we eat,
and then we we film something.
>> You know what's one of the ones I like?
Rob, can you go back? It was I think it
was a skiing one or or a snowboarding
one. Keep going the other way, Rob. Keep
going. Lower. Lower.
>> You did a snowboarding clip.
>> Yeah. Go.
>> It's got to come up. Keep going. Keep
going. Keep going. It was It was
hilarious the way you post. I don't know
which one it is. If it's still going,
>> go down.
>> Go down a little bit more, Rob.
>> Yeah. Here. right there. Click on that
one. Look at this. This is the one that
I commented you. Look at this.
>> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> The the last part when I
>> That's the best part.
Oh,
>> thank
this is the thing getting the eyeballs
and the attention.
Say
>> one and a half million likes. Rob, click
on the views. Click on Just click on the
1.5 million. If you click on the 1.5 to
the right, it'll tell you. Look at this.
Uh, it doesn't tell you. I don't know
how many views it is. It's in the tens
of millions.
>> More than 20 something millions. So, so
by the way, is it at a point for you
right now where
because are you starting to make money
doing content or not yet? Are you doing
are you getting millions of dollar
sponsorship money or not yet?
>> Oh, right now. Yes,
>> you are now.
>> Yeah. Well, because last year I signed
all my contracts, but uh in one month
they're going to be done and I already
like instead of like 500,000 I'm I'm
going to make 3 million.
>> Three million a month in sponsorship.
>> No, no. I'm approximating on one of the
saying like for example if I made like
500,000 a year from one brand now I'm
like making 3 million 4 million.
>> Yeah. So so yeah because if you think
about like the way Jake Paul did it or
Logan did or some of these guys did it.
You're on track to being one of these
guys that's going to get you know 20 30
40 50 million 100 million followers.
Like literally you yourself with the way
you're creating content.
>> Yeah. But uh to gain followers is not
easy. You just got to like uh for
example give a car for the followers and
like okay follow me I'm going to give
you a car and you're going to gain like
5 million followers. It's it's easy but
I don't want to do that because I'm just
who wants to follow not like that I'm
going to give them something if they
like my content they they going to
follow me. So and uh I before I I I was
not thinking about oh I got to make
money from the social media this that I
was just having fun you know and uh it's
uh not my biggest goal right now to make
money so my biggest goal enjoy my life I
enjoy my life I fight I wrestle I I
travel around the world yeah the worst
thing I don't I don't spend too much
time with my family mom I I got kids So,
but uh you know, I'm 29 right now. I'm
telling them when I'm going to be 36,
37, I'm not going to like train anymore
and I'm going to be with you all day.
So, you're going to get tired from me.
So, enjoy your life
>> for now until 6 years from now.
>> So, now your story, I've I've heard it
from a lot of different people, you
know, uh uh story of you used to be a
hockey player and then all of a sudden
you got into fighting. So, maybe tell me
a little bit about your upbringing.
>> Yeah. Well, I was born in Georgia. We
moved to Russia for the good life, you
know. Um,
and then I went to K. I didn't like I
like K, but it was too far. And then I
started wrestle because it's close to my
home. We start start I was starting
wrestling and I could wrestle so good
when I was kid. But like my coach always
tell me you got to cut weight because
you got to be lighter and I was hit I
was hitting this sport because of cut
weight. But nowadays if someone askked
me as a kid kid shouldn't cut weight
because it's the worst thing ever for
the kid and I couldn't I could not eat
like three four days as like 8 years kid
can imagine like what stress
>> 8 years old so you started training very
early
>> yeah I started six I started training
six and from 6 to 9 or 10 I was like
beating everybody on the wrestling and
when I was 10 I was playing for like
from six or seven years I I wrestle like
professional already but like I used I I
play hockey in my backyard with my
friends because all my uh classmates
were hockey player I'm from Habarov it's
like a cold place in Russia it's like
north north like the coldest place in
Russia and everybody
>> not an Armenian community
>> no no no
a lot of Armenian only Russian people so
they they play all day hockey
uh in the winter time and my friends was
uh their hockey players. So I was
playing with them and then when I was 9
or 10, one of the coach see how I'm
playing on the backyard hockey and they
said you got something special like uh
do you want to come and play like with
professional? I said how like they start
when they were five six you got to start
earlier when you're in hockey and I
started 10
and uh and even I couldn't pick it up
until 17. So I was playing professional
from 10 to 17 hockey.
>> You were playing professional hockey
from 10 to 7.
>> Yeah. I wanted to go NHL. So my dad even
was saying like whatever you want I send
you Canada, USA just if you want to play
uh in NHL. So you got to go there. I
said the I like to be here. So but I was
kid I didn't know what I should do. So
if I was smart I should tell to my dad
to send me to US or uh to Canada to play
here. Were you that good that you think
you could have made it in the NHL?
>> Uh, I was good. I was good. And uh my
goal was the hockey. And then when I was
17, I understood like I cannot be a good
hiker player. And uh and I said, "Okay,
it's done. I'm going to work with my
dad." And I was working 3 months with my
dad and said, "No, this is not my thing.
I I like to be in the sport because it's
easier for me. You wake up, you know
your time, your trains one or two times
a day, you chill all day, you're like
clean, you know, eat clean food. But
when you're in construction business,
you wake up at 6:00, you don't have a
schedule. You just drive everywhere,
like talk to people, like help your dad,
you know, they don't care about their
body. They just work all day and like
it's a it's not the best job. And I
said, "No, I want to go back to sport."
And I said, "My dad, can I go to
grappling school?" And he said, "Yeah,
do it." And uh I went to grappling and I
I could do so good because I trained
when I was from 6 to 9 wrestling and I I
could pick it up so fast and grappling
was just starting in Russia.
>> So from 9 to 17, you didn't do any
grappling or wrestling?
>> Nothing. Nothing.
>> So only 6 to9 wrestled, then 9 to 17
hockey, and then you come back to
grappling in 17.
>> So in one year, I I I was a Russian
champion. So yeah, it was like a
everybody was surprised how I made it
and like and grappling for me was boring
and I I see like someone is fighting and
I said, "Okay, I got I asked my dad, can
I do one fight in MMA?" He said, "You're
stupid. They're going to break your hat.
Why you need that?" I said, "Just one
fight." I I I I like when they people go
to to the cage, you know, with music.
And I watch once when I was like 17 and
they said, "I want to do this once in my
life." Who' you watch? What fight did
you watch at 7?
>> Uh, it's a Dagistani guy. He was walking
uh to his to the cage with the good
music, you know. I said it it it make
make me so excited and I said I want to
do this in my life
>> just because the walk out.
>> Yeah, walk out. Yeah. I don't know why
the walk out and people like crowd watch
you and I don't know like I like it so
much and I said my dad can I do once and
he said just once and my mom was crying
all day don't do that because someone
going to break your hat so you're going
to be stupid early all your life
>> now have you been a fighter like were
you a fighter or mainly wrestling would
you get into a lot of fist fights or no
>> no no I didn't have experience I I was
like a grappler and then I want to
transition to MMA just for one one for
one Fine. So, and uh thank God I won my
first one and then they offered me right
away the second one was the guy who has
11 or 10 fights professional and I
didn't have a coach who said no, don't
do that. I had like I I have a like a
strong heart, you know. I don't care who
I I'm going to fight. I said if he wants
to fight me, I'll go because I'm I was
young, no experience. Nobody tell me you
shouldn't do that. you got to uh box
first,
get experience, and then you you can go
to fight like these. I said, "Okay, I
don't care." Like, I just go and take
and wrestle him. And I went there in 15
or 20 seconds. He knocked me out. My dad
said, "What are you doing? Like I told
you, don't go there. It's not your
thing." And I was so mad and I said,
"Okay, give me one year and uh can you
send me to
Thailand?" So I flew to Thailand. I
stayed there one year and I came back,
beat him, this guy that he knocked me
out.
>> What did you do in Thailand for one
year?
>> I was training. I was coming back uh uh
for competition to Russia and then back
to to Thailand.
>> How intense was the training in
Thailand?
>> Was hard was hard. So hard. And I didn't
know how to train. I was training all
day. I felt like a professional fighter.
They go to the gym in the morning and
then come in the evening back. So I was
in the gym all day. I didn't know like I
got to go there do one training and then
evening and then rest and then evening I
I went there from 9 to 11 it was
jiujitsu from 12 to 2 it was MMA
and then from 5 to 6 it was sparring and
I was doing like all all that uh
trainings
>> every day.
>> Every day yeah uh only uh Sunday day
off.
>> Who who told you about that place? Uh I
was watching on the YouTube. I didn't
know even where where that place. I just
know it was in the island Puket. And I
landed there. I was asking everybody
where's Tiger Mai and they nobody knew
that. And then and then one of the the
taxi driver he he drove me there. It was
like 30 minutes from the airport or
>> Did you go by yourself or did you go
with a
>> No, alone. Alone. I was there alone.
Alone.
>> By yourself? You're saying you're going
to Thailand based on a video you saw on
YouTube?
>> Yeah. Nobody. Nobody. Yeah. Yeah. So,
>> so you're training there and then you're
you're now at the same time are you
coming back and forth to Russia or No.
>> Yeah. I was going back back to Russia,
beat somebody and then come back and
then in one year exactly same day I beat
the guy who knocked me out. I choke him
out and then my dad said, "Okay, you you
beat him. That's it." But I was I was
winning for one year five fights. I was
Russian champion MMA, master of sport of
MMA. And like I I asked the one guy, I
want to retire because my dad doesn't I
was 19 and he said you shouldn't do
that. You have like a good potential
like you can be in UFC and uh don't do
that. I said what is UFC like? What are
you talking about? I'm just fighting.
Yeah. And then I flew to Korea. I beat
the guy in Korea. And then one of my
manager said like keep doing because
you're seven and one. uh you can be like
a good MMA fighter and you can you can
you can be in UFC. So and then I w and I
won started beating everybody and I was
like 30 13 win streaked 30 win streak
and they signed me to in UFC for two
weeks before.
>> So at what point did Dana know who you
were? Do you have an idea when the UFC
found out who this kid is Arman that's
beating everybody up? Uh yeah because
the
they signed me before
it it was the second second event in
Russia. UFC UFC in Russia and they they
were looking for someone from there. So
and they they got me there and they it
was short notice before two weeks they
they told me before fight but still you
know I said I got to take this chance
because you never know what's what going
to be tomorrow. Maybe they're never
going to call me again. And is this a
Islam fight?
>> Yeah, it's Islam fight. I I went there
and like my manager it's Islam. I said I
don't care who is Islam and who is the
Habib. I don't care like I need the want
to be in UFC. I knew they give you they
give you contract not for one fight.
They give you contract for four fights.
So if you go there perform very well and
I knew I could beat him. I don't know
why in my mind I was so confident.
>> Yeah. When
>> is that you or someone's telling you
this? Like you have to you the
confidence is you.
>> Yeah. Just me.
>> Where where did you where did the
confidence come from?
>> I think from my blood I don't know
because the where I born uh hard
lifestyle you know the my my parents
they they came from nothing probably
from that that you got to take risk and
uh and uh do what you got to do. You
know
>> your dad seems like an interesting guy.
Is he very tough? Is he like if he's a
tough guy? Is he he's tough. he can work
24/7 and never complain. And uh when I
was growing up, I was watching what he's
doing, you know. And like he he he never
buys for himself. Nothing. He just think
about us for for our future. And uh for
example, if you ask him like I want to
buy this car or this. Yeah. He said buy
it. But for him, he never going to buy
for him like a car or what.
>> Simple guy.
>> Yeah. I mean when he was like 40
something I said like that why you you
don't want to buy a car he said my time
is left when I wanted to to have a cars
when I was 25 23 24 uh that m moment I
didn't have money but now I don't I
don't need that mo but I want you to
enjoy because I didn't enjoy that time
>> how many siblings
>> I got the older brother and younger
sister
>> so that's your older brother
>> to your right what what does he do does
he work with dad or
>> he he works with that.
>> He works with that. So, rumor has it
your dad's very wealthy.
>> No, not very wealthy. He's okay. We we
good lifestyle. We we travel around the
world. We drive any cars we want, but
like we don't have like I don't know
billions.
>> You're not billionaires?
>> No.
>> So broke like a half a billion. Like a
few hundred million
>> about. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So funny.
Now did you always uh have a like I have
a I have four kids but out of my two
boys one of them Arman he is such a
simple life we can go anywhere he will
wear flip flops just relax you know he's
happy my younger son Dylan 12 he has a
very expensive taste he always wants the
best of everything you always like that
did you always want the best of
everything
>> yes me yes but my older brother same
like my dad so he never he never go and
like spend so much money or something.
He doesn't care what he's wearing. He
never goes to the like a
Rolex store and buy for him watches.
That watches he's wearing it's mine. I
gift it to him. And he's same as my dad.
But me, I'm opposite. My sister is
opposite to my sister, she likes like
fleshy things. I like fleshy things. But
my dad and my brother, they don't care
like what watch they have, what clothes
they wear. They just they don't care.
But it's uh Yeah. But they're it's kind
for me it's I'm not I'm not doing for
anybody. I do for myself. I like watch.
I like clothes. I wear not like show up,
you know.
>> Yeah. What did you learn from mom? What
did you learn from dad?
>> From dad I learn
you got you from that
like uh
you you got to work to get something.
No, not not not not someone going to
gift you something. Not don't wait like
to anybody to gift you or like to tell
you you got to do this that you got to
take it and do it by yourself like how
you think is good. If you fail, stand up
and go try it again. So that's why I
don't I don't have too much patient. If
I want to do this, I'll do it like my
dad said, you know.
>> How about mom?
My mom uh
my mom athletic. She's she she she likes
uh working out. She likes to take care
of her body. Like I take from my from my
dad like a hard work from my mom
athletic thing. So So she doesn't eat
like from when I was young. I never eat
like a uh sausages. Never drink uh uh uh
juices juice. never drink in our house.
It's like water or like a homemade
juice, you know. We don't So my mom, she
always like take care of us so good and
like uh she works out every day and from
her I took took that.
>> Really? Was she an athlete before or
like did she
>> No, she just like it. So when we go out
when we go to vacation, so my dad my my
dad is sleeping, my sister is sleeping,
but uh me, my mother, my my mom, we go
out running or like walking and she
likes to to work out.
>> Very cool. So So the work ethic from
dad, the athletic side from mom,
>> that's amazing. And then you like to
find her things like your like your
younger sister, the two of you guys
together.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But she's lazy, so she
doesn't like to work out.
Yeah,
>> just watching it right now.
>> Yeah. So, what can I say? She's lazy.
She doesn't like workout. She she she
likes like the older brother going to
give her everything and like she doesn't
like even uh study. So, we cannot like
um
>> Are you okay with that?
>> We tried to push it. It didn't It didn't
work. What we can do? So, now we're
looking for what she likes to do. So
we're trying to open for her like salon,
beauty salon, and she likes beauty
things. So
>> it's great.
>> Yeah. So we you cannot like push. For
example,
if I'm going to have a boy, I want him
to be a fighter, right? I'm going to see
if he doesn't like that. I'm not going
to push him. He's never going to be like
he's not never going to be a fighter.
>> Yeah. If he doesn't want to, you can't
force him to do it. I tried to force my
oldest son to play uh
>> baseball and he just hated it. He's
like, "Nah, I'm not interested. You're
interested. I'm gonna I'm gonna fight."
He's a fighter. He does Muay Thai. Uh he
couldn't stand doing jiu-jitsu. I put
him in jiu-jitsu and my dad, his
grandpa's videotaping him because he's
in a class down the street here and one
of the girls he in the class there was
one girl and this girl this one time is
teaming up with him and she's on top of
him and he's just laying like this. He
says, "Look, I want to learn how to
fight so people don't come close to me."
Yeah.
>> I don't want people come close to me.
So, he likes Muai more. But going back
to it, when you were talking about the
fight with uh Islam that you had, you
went the distance if I'm not mistaken,
right? Is is the
>> Yeah, it was the
>> three rounds or three rounds you guys
went the distance. Yeah.
>> What did you learn from that fight
afterwards? Cuz you only had two weeks
and this is the guy everybody's fearing.
You face him.
>> What What clues did he leave with you?
Uh from that fight I learned
uh you shouldn't be so so confident. You
always got to got to like think twice,
you know. Don't don't be don't u
underestimated your your your fighter.
Even like last week I was like last
Saturday I was uh wrestling with the old
legend. He's old but still like I was
doing warm up like I supposed to do. I
was preparing the same. I was cutting
same weight because every everything can
happen in the in the fight.
>> So after that fight, yeah, you you never
got to underestimate your fighter.
>> Yeah. And with the Fab, if you're
talking about Faber, I'm assuming,
right? And in the fight with Faber, this
one clip went viral. Was the fight in
Philadelphia? I don't know why I think
it was in Philadelphia.
>> Was it was in Philadelphia, right?
>> Yeah.
>> And and and there's a clip of you, Rob.
I don't know if you have it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. where you know on is this it
make this a little bit bigger Rob.
>> So what happened to you? Were Were you
Was this intentional? Was it accidental?
>> Accidental.
>> That's insane. Not intentional at all.
>> No. I mean you got to do a show, right?
If like it was like a simple uh
wrestling, nobody going to talk about
that. You got to do something unusual.
Did that hurt anything like when you
fell? Adrenaline, nothing. No injuries.
>> No, no, no. We know how to fell.
>> And him as well. He's okay as well.
>> Yeah, he's good. I'm going to send him a
gift.
>> You're going to send him a gift?
>> Yeah.
>> What's the gift?
>> We'll see how much RF pay me.
>> Does this actually pay well? Is it a
good paying fight? The the wrestling.
>> Yeah, wrestling. I get paid good.
>> Like what's good? I mean they don't want
to tell me how much they pay me because
the other fight other wrestlers going to
wants the same money so they trying to
but like you can buy a good PC Philip
>> you can buy a good PC Philip that can
range
>> no not like yours
>> you can but you have a nice one
>> like like this one yeah you can buy but
like this one you got to do like a 67
>> 67 to get this one he knows watches. Uh,
so from your experience with UFC, cuz
UFC publicizes the biggest payday,
right? What's the most money you made
with UFC in a fight?
>> Was UFC?
>> Um, more than a half a million.
>> More than a half a million in a fight.
Okay.
>> And the last person you fought, um,
>> Dan Hooker.
>> Dan Hooker, which was about a year ago,
right? He's the one that you headbutted
in the the
>> pre before Wayne's because I hate this
guy. And then and then he tried to
flinch me and then I said sometimes I
cannot control myself. If some if if the
guy is good, cool. I'm cool too. But if
someone wants to like flinch you and
like make you scared like I'm not going
to step back straight forward
>> to him.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. So this guy, you didn't like him
from the beginning? No, I didn't like
because we were talking trash about he
was talking bad about me this that and
like and then now I like him because I
beat him.
>> Yeah. It's always like that. Once you
beat him, you're friends with them,
right? It's different when you're
fighting.
>> Yeah. So, but he has a like a bad mouth.
>> Arman, what what do you think normal
people don't know about Armenians
that there's certain rules with
Armenians? You can't curse. You know
what I'm saying? Like there's certain
certain things with Armenians that if
you say for whatever reason we tend to
get more angry than other communities.
Why do you think that is?
>> Uh because of uh the place where we grew
up and second one is a genetic uh test
that we have. It's from there coming.
>> You think that's what it is?
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> Yeah. Cuz in Armenia
>> Yeah. Cuz if you go to Armenia, I mean
the all the places Armenia, Georgia,
Dagistan, Chachchna,
it's like kind of same culture everybody
has. If you go there in the village, the
the kids is fighting to each other and
they grow up like this. And then when
they go to the city, they have that
mentality like like you know and um
that's why the best fighters they coming
from from there. If they going to sign a
lot of Dagistani, Chin, uh, uh,
Georgian, Armenian fighter, they going
to take over all UFC.
>> No, but what what I'm asking is I'm
asking more about from the side of um,
you know, like in in Americans, they'll
say, "Hey, mother, you know, they'll
just kind of
>> they just talk and like
>> you just talk."
>> Yeah. And but but if you do that to even
when Connor was doing it to Kabib,
Kabib's like listening to everything
he's saying you don't talk about my
father, my religion, nothing like that.
Armenians have a side of that as well.
>> Yeah.
>> Where you can't you can't speak a
certain way. So how do you you're in the
game of promoting guys are going to talk
trash. How do you process that? Do you
do you mentally set it aside and say I
can't take this thing personally? How do
you deal with it?
>> No, I can deal it so easy. But sometimes
for the show you got to do something.
You got to if you think like for example
Hhabib he had already name big name and
he he shouldn't do anything. If he's
just listen him it's okay. But for
example right now I I got to do
something like crazy things that that
going to bring a lot of eyes and then I
when I when I like uh fight or something
they already know who am I, you know.
And um
uh that's why sometimes people think I'm
too crazy, but it's like
I don't know. Sometimes I say, "Okay,
I'm not going to do anything, but like I
cannot control myself so much." So I
need someone to who is going to stop me.
>> Does it help to
when the opponent is somebody you really
want to destroy or does it work against
you? You know what I'm saying? Like does
it help if you hate the guy you're
facing against or it doesn't matter
>> when it doesn't matter when you're in
the cage you're calm you don't care but
so in the cage it's completely different
game it's just a it's a it's the no
talking nothing it's just like a fight
and uh if for example I hate the Ben
Hooker I used to hate him and when I was
in the cage I was so calm like I was
controlling myself because it's a fight
you cannot do like if you're going going
to be not calm, you're going to lose,
you're going to uh gas out. So that's
why you got to control yourself and like
be um calm. So it's important.
>> Who Who did you fight that would talk to
you? Are there fighters that would talk
to you in the middle of the fight that
that would try to get to you or No.
>> Yeah, sometimes. But I don't care what
they say. So in the cage, it's easy. You
know, you can beat them. Out of cage,
yeah, they it's uh it's hard to control
yourself because you cannot beat him
right away. That's why he can talk a
lot. But in the cage, he can talk
whatever he want. You can just smash
him.
>> Yeah. I remember uh uh when Khabib would
fight, he was talking. He would talk a
lot and he would talk to Connor as well
in the fight. You know, there would be a
certain level of conversation with them,
but that's not your style. You're not
the one. You're just focused on the
fight uh versus your opponent.
>> Yeah, mostly. Yeah. But never know. So,
>> you never know.
>> You never know. Yeah.
>> You could surprise somebody.
>> Yeah, for sure. Have you ever uh
grappled or wrestled or done anything
with Kabib or no?
>> No. Oh, his teammates? Yes. A lot.
>> His teammates? Yes. But not him
directly.
>> Not yet. Uh I came a little bit late
later. So he's already retired and uh
coaching his uh uh uh cousins, but in
the future for sure, I'm going to fight
his cousins or somebody because they
they he has a good team.
>> Do you guys ever communicate? Have you
guys ever communicate?
>> We cool. We cool. I'm cool with habib
Islam with everybody
>> with this whole camp.
>> Yeah. Because uh we live in the same
same country and we have same culture
and we don't like pass the lane, you
know, you got to respect.
>> And right now you're training with uh uh
>> Hamzad.
>> Hamzad. Yeah. How's the training with
him?
>> Oh, so hard. Hamzad the guy he I thought
like I train a lot. So I have the same
problem like Hamzad. If nobody gonna
control me what I'm doing, I'm going to
overt train. Overtrain always. And when
you overt train, you cannot perform. So
that's why you need a good coach. Hamzad
same. Uh
he he works so hard and you got to stop
him. So that's why
he like three four five fights ago he
couldn't make weight. He pulled out, got
injured because he always overtrained.
But now he has a good team and everybody
control him. No, not not overtrained.
>> So it's important. So it's interesting.
So overtraining works against you when
it comes down to the fight.
>> Yeah. When you're young, you can
overtrain because your body can like
take it. But right now when you're 30,
31, 32, you cannot do the same when
you're 18. So that's why now you got to
take care of your body and uh train
smart. Especially we cut a lot of weight
too. So he cuts maybe like 15 kg. It's
like about 30 pounds.
>> Wow. In In what time? What time frame?
>> Like one month.
>> In one month. That's insane to go
through that.
>> Yeah.
>> And what what do you notice when you
you've trained with a lot of different
people, I'm assuming over the years?
>> Yeah.
>> What are some of the big names you've
trained against? Not fought, but trained
with.
>> Yeah. But Hamzad, I think, the biggest
name.
>> Biggest name.
>> Yeah. Right now.
>> How does that help you training against
somebody his size?
I mean when I watch his training what
he's doing on the sparring so I was try
to take something from him you know
because he has a good u good wrestling
good good striking it's always good to
have a teammator like him and he's a
he's mindset he has a different mindset
like not everybody he never watch his
opponent fights he don't care what he's
going to do for example me I sit and
watch like Okay, hooker. He does the
like kick from the lefty righty. He does
this that like I'm going to do this.
He's going to kick me this. Okay, let's
train. He's uh like a do a lot of
straight kicks and I do defense during
the training. But this guy, he doesn't
know like what even like a Strickland
does or like his opponent, he never
watch them and he doesn't care what he's
going to do. He cares what he's going to
do to him. So he he has his own game
plan just on what he's going to do.
>> Wow.
>> So that's why he's different. That's why
he's a champion. Different.
>> So he he doesn't study his opponents at
all.
>> At all. Yeah. So
me I'm opposite. I'm like looking what
he's doing this that switch stand. When
he throw like one, two, he's going this
way or that way.
He is different. Yeah. That I'm taking
from the from him. Nowadays, I don't
think about my opponent so much. I watch
once and that's it. So, I let my coaches
think about that.
>> Yeah, that's that's pretty that's pretty
wild to be thinking about because
typically in every sport, it's like
study your opponent. We watch tape, we
watch this, we watch that.
>> I think I I watch more uh his opponent
than him for sure. I watch like what
Strickland does that he's fighting next
month.
But uh
>> why did he bring you in? Because if he's
fighting Strickland, why why train with
you? Of course, you're one of the best
in the world and in your weight class,
you're you're you're feared by
everybody. But why bring you in?
>> Uh we're good friends and he he has a
fight in US and he asked me like where I
should train. So he came here one year
ago and he liked it to train with me
with my coaches the the place where I
train and uh he feels free here because
he's superstar in Russia in Oi UAE here
in Newport nobody like bother him so he
can focus on on his thing and uh uh he
likes the energy he likes to to be uh
>> how fun is he how fun is he without uh
you know with the camera off with nobody
being there Is he as fun as he seems
like he is or is he very serious?
>> So this you can see him once he he can
be the funniest guy ever but you can see
him in one hour he's going to be the
scariest guy ever. So he he can change
his mind his mood so fast and I ask my
guys like my friends they tell me you're
same. So you can be funny in the morning
and then in the evening you come and
like like why you doing this like and
like you're so like have a good you have
bad bad mood. So maybe because of we are
fighter fighters or I don't know like
he's same one day you cannot even talk
to him because he say hi how are you
good that's it so he doesn't talk one
day he never stop you can talk like
three four hours
>> it's funny that that's a that's a very
common pattern uh with a lot of uh
creative minds who wouldn't stop and
were not happy with uh you know their
level of contentment was so low they
wanted to win at highest level and they
couldn't stop.
>> Athletes typically the best ones have a
bit of that mindset.
>> You know, Brady, if you're around Brady,
there's moments that he's got a fun
side, but you know, he can all of a
sudden be a psycho. It's like, "Hey, why
are you guys sitting around so happy?
We're losing. Let's get our act
together." It's a very very common
pattern with uh highest level winners.
So, for you, what is what is next for
you? Because there's a lot there's a lot
of people that want to see you. You're
not on the White House card. I thought
you were going to be on the White House
card. I thought the big fight would have
been, you know, a lot of names with you
being included in it. What's the next
big one for you?
>> I'm a backup for the White House. So,
main event in my weight.
>> You are.
>> Yeah. So, if something happened uh on
the main event, if someone pull out or
>> is this public information?
>> It's not public, but you still tell me
if if someone like
>> Oh, buddy. Don't say that. Are you
serious?
>> Yeah. If someone pull out, but they got
to get injured.
>> Like, well, I mean, there's a big one.
if a guy pulls out like you.
>> Yeah. So that's why I'm I'm I'm flying
out tomorrow to back to Kali and
training. So
>> wait, if if accidentally
GI or Tapora pulls out, you're in
>> Yeah, 100%.
>> Oh my god.
>> Yeah.
Yeah. Uh that's the goal. So we never
know. Uh it's a dangerous sport, but
these guys, they train so
they don't train hard. So
lower chance
>> lower chance of them.
>> Yeah.
>> So meaning the the chance of them
getting injured is not high. They're
probably going to take the fight.
>> Yeah. It's not high because they both
the Tapur is just hitting pads. He
doesn't do anything else.
>> Ki he's super old. He just maybe like
playing. He doesn't want to like have a
strong strong sparrings because it's
>> it's not it's not good for him right
now.
Well, for me, I I um the challenge is I
don't know if
Dana would be good with Justin dropping
out
>> because it's a USA flag and it's 250.
>> It's okay. I'll fight for you. USA.
>> I'll fight for you.
>> And uh for sure, for sure. Uh they're
going to be proud more than for Gi. I'm
going to show better fight than Gi.
>> If you and Taporio
>> Yeah, 100%. I think the world wants to
see that.
>> Yeah. Everybody's waiting for that
fight. So,
but if if it's not happen now, it's
going to eventually it's going to
happen. And I take my time. I learn
something new. I getting better every
day.
>> I'm not like, "Oh, why it doesn't
happen?" Like, it didn't happen in
January. Why didn't I'm not mad. I'm
just waiting for my chance. And u
>> Did they call you at all for this fight
or No, for this card. Were you at all?
>> Yes. I uh they called me for the you see
Chandler
>> Rafie and Chandler
>> they wanted me put against the Chandler
and then they understood like it's bad
bad for Chandler and he represent us
it's like 99.9 that I'm beating him so
and then they put Ruffy so if someone
get hurt in Ruffy or Chandler they might
call me too. So
>> Oh, so either one of them they might
call you.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But ideal fight for you there's
two Yeah.
>> You want the title fight?
>> Yeah, I won the title fight.
>> Yeah. So, and and for you, you in your
mind, you told the story at the
beginning. You said you went and fought
your first guy, you lost, you went to
Thailand, you trained for a year, then
you came back and you beat the other
guy, and you uh I think submission you
said, right, that you did.
>> Yeah.
>> To the guy.
>> Is that story going to repeat itself
with Islam when you go back and face him
off? Is that kind of how you see that
story taking place
>> right now? No. because I'm I'm thinking
about that title fight in my way to 155.
>> He moved up, right? He moved up 170.
>> Yeah, but if he stay long long in this
in this game. Yeah, I would like to go
up and fight him. But right now, my goal
is uh to get the title fight in 155
probably. So there is probably in this
summer and the end of this summer or
they give me BM BMF title in June 11.
Oh, dude, you're so qualified for BMF
type of a
>> Yeah. So, they uh either BMF July or
title fight in the end of this summer or
September, October.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well, I mean, listen, uh I love
Justin, of course. He he's a fan
favorite. He was at the UFC in Miami
when we were here just last week, and
when the audience sees him, he's got a
big fan base, but he's at a different
age. Uh 37. Taporio's how old right now?
Is he 30? Is it 29 or 30?
>> 29.
>> 29. So he's 29 and and you're 29.
>> Yeah.
>> What a perfect uh matchup. I mean, if if
that's the main if you if you guys end
up Well, something needs to happen last
minute for that to be the fight. Um but
that'd be a big one. When you watch
Taporio, what what do you think about
Tapori? Because I had Tapori here on the
podcast. We had a very good conversation
together.
>> Different kind of a fighter.
>> Yeah.
>> Right. Different kind of a fighter. good
good fighter, good mindset, um
good boxer. He so he used to be a
wrestler and then he understood
wrestling is a waste of energy and then
he started box. He improved his boxing.
Now he box people
because uh it's hard to wrestle and box
you know 25 minutes
unless if you're Habib or Hamza. So they
can wrestle 25 minutes non-stop.
Uh
but nowadays he just do good good thing.
It's a it's a box. That's it. He doesn't
kick. He doesn't like wrestle.
So his main thing it's a box. For me
it's easy because I have a good kicks
that I can stay on the kick distance and
if he comes with box I wrestle him or I
clinch him. So they know that too. They
they gonna try to avoid they're going to
try to move up after this fight. He's
going to say
they cannot fight me because it's like
it's like uh even his teammator they
know it's tough fight. It's a tough
fight. Why we should take the tie fight
if we can fight with Olivera uh Gi the
guys who is like in the end of their
career and they cannot do everything and
they have a bad chin. they they drop so
much. So if he if they going to hit
them, they going to they're going to um
lose, you know. So
uh yeah, that's the main thing. So
probably
he's going to get the title. He's going
to defend the title and say, "I'm going
to leave this title."
>> He's going to leave this title. So
>> uh it's my opinion if he if he's on on
the camera, he's saying, "I don't care.
I fight Arman, but when the time comes
to fight Arman, he's always like a uh
trying to find excuses.
>> Well, you're a little bit you're you're
you're you're the one fight nobody
wants, right? You're the guy that
everybody wants to delay, but he's also
formidable. I actually think if the two
of you guys fought, it would be uh one
of the highest uh uh grossing
viewership. I think it can be the
matchups because I don't think either
one of you guys uh are when Taporio
fights he's also good for the fans.
>> Yeah.
>> Like he doesn't show up. There were
certain fighters back in the days that
they only fight for, you know, points
scoring. They play it safe and when you
fight, you're not going to play safe
either. I think it would make for an
hell of a fight for a lot of people. A
lot of people probably want that fight.
Uh uh what has Tuporia said about you
when your name comes up? Because I'm
sure you watch everything he says about
you in interviews. last time he was on
the stream. Uh I don't know. He said
knocking me out or something. I don't
remember to be honest.
>> He said he would knock you out.
>> I don't remember to be honest, but he
said easy. He No, he said I think easy
I'll take this fight.
>> Yeah. Yeah, probably. No. No. He said
what he's going to do? He's going to
wrestle me. I'm going to defend. What?
What else? He cannot box and uh I'm
going to knock him out or something like
that.
>> Rob, is this is this to pour you on the
podcast?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Okay. I don't remember what he said, but
I do remember we talked about Arman. Go
for it. Can you look at that rap?
>> I'm curious now because I is
>> Charles is number Oh, Arman is number
two.
>> Armon number two.
>> So would you fight an Arman before you
go like let's just say Dana says I want
you to fight Arman before you fight
Islam. Would you entertain that?
>> He wouldn't he wouldn't tell me that.
>> He wouldn't tell you that.
>> No.
>> Dana would say Islam.
>> He would say for the belt.
>> Yeah.
>> I think so as well because you're
undefeated.
>> Of course. Yeah,
>> there's no way that I have to fight to
to the number one contender. I have to
fight directly for the belt.
>> How soon you think that would happen?
>> Personally, I don't know.
>> The rap.
>> Yeah, that that moment he Islam was the
champion. So that's why. So I was number
one
>> and Islam moved up.
>> Moved up and uh Yeah. So and I supposed
to fight him and UFC decided to put him
versus Oliver. How much how much you
when when it comes on to fighting,
Arman, do they call you and they just
tell you here's who you're fighting or
do they call you and say between these
two who would you rather fight? They
tell you the fight or do you have a
choice at times?
>> No, they never tell me. Uh they don't
they they never give me like two names,
only one name. Here's your fight.
>> Yeah. And they'll take it. And then no
matter when they call you, you going to
take the fight because I
>> uh I I turned down just one fight
because when I was number 10 or I was
number one and they they gave me like
number 10 or 11, the guy who was losing
everybody.
>> Yeah, because Dana did say one time he
says with Arman, he doesn't take all the
fights. We want people to take the
fights. I think he made a comment about
that uh uh in the past. H how's the
relationship with Dana?
>> I'm cool with him.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. So, I'm good with uh I'm good with
everybody in UFC and um
uh I turn down the fight because
they never give me fight when I was
number 10 or number 11 with number one
contender. Why I beat number nine? Why I
beat number eight? Why why you give this
guy like a the present to fight with
number one contender and he's nobody and
he lose to Alivera, he lost to Darush,
he lose to Hooker and I beat everybody
and you're going to give me this this
fight and I said I don't want to give me
the the better fighters like from top
five that I deserve it.
>> What where were you ranked when he gave
you number 10?
>> I was number one.
>> Oh, so that's when he Oh,
>> that's just one fight in my life. I
turned out once once in my life and I
became the worst person ever.
>> But you have to know that's Dana though.
You know, Dana, if Dana calls, you got
to say yes.
>> I think I think Dana Dana, he doesn't he
doesn't know what's going on. Uh uh what
fights is offering me because he he's on
he decided on the the title fights even.
I don't think so. He decided tit title
fights. They just give him like this
card. He said yes or no or maybe he can
switch because the the hunter and
matchmakers, they do all this work.
>> Mhm. He he doesn't he doesn't do
anything. He just run out like a
business or like a sponsorships like a
big deals. I don't I think he he's on
different level right now and he doesn't
know what's going on over there.
>> You don't think he you don't think he's
Well, he did say he's no longer
negotiating contracts.
>> Yeah.
>> He said moving forward it's Hunter and
other people that are doing it. No
longer me. I think he just said that
recently.
>> Yeah. And I don't think so. is like u
in uh like uh making fights because he
has a matchmakers and the hunter
probably they just give him the the card
and he say yes or no pro I think I don't
know
>> because it takes so much time can
imagine you like how much time he has
like to make all these fights
>> let me ask you a question can are you
also a fan of the fight are you a fan of
UFC
>> yes I'm a fan of UFC
>> so you you're a fighter but you're also
a fan you watch it as well
>> yes
>> okay If I have a time, I always fly to
Vegas and watch. Yeah. So, thank God UFC
give me good tickets.
I'm still I'm still on
still alive.
>> So
So, let me ask you this. I It's It's
almost historically
all the best fighters in every weight
class had a little bit of conflict with
Dana.
>> It's not the regular ones. It's always
the best ones.
>> Yeah. that a little bit of issue. It's
almost like it's it's expected as and
I'm talking as a fan. You're on the
inside. I'm not on the inside. I'm just
a fan that goes and and uh
>> supports what's going on. Do you see
that as a common pattern? Like uh you
know the the faces of the fighting game
typically have a little bit of conflict
with the top of UFC.
>> Yeah. Because everybody wants to make
more money.
So they hear like how much the NBA
players, how much the football players
making and UFC fighters wants to make a
lot of money too. And and then they
started like do the thing. Jon Jones
not just he wants big money.
Tapura for the white house. He want
Islam. He asked the big money. Everybody
like asking for big money. That's why
probably they argue.
So you think it's the money part? Well,
let me ask you.
>> Yeah, 100% money.
>> Let's say I'm negotiating on behalf of
Dana. For the next two minutes, I work
for Dana.
>> For me, they send me contract. I sign
and give it back. I don't even watch how
much they
>> That's exactly what them
if they were to say, okay, something
happened to Justin. I want you to be on
the White House card, but we're not
paying you nothing. Would you take the
fight?
>> 100%.
>> So, let me get this straight. I mean,
this is very important because we can
save UFC some money right now. Yeah,
>> if if they called you from UFC right now
and they said take the fight against
Ilia for zero. You take it, don't pay me
nothing.
>> I got to watch was the in my contract to
fight for the title. I don't know how
much I I'm getting paid. So, because
last time before the hooker fight, they
they give me contract. I said, "Okay,
I'll sign it because I want to be a a a
normal guy in UC because I don't have
too much tools." They give me contract.
I signed. It was a good money for and I
just signed it. I didn't say, "Oh, add
me like 200 more because I want to more
my." I said, "Okay, I want to fight for
the title." They give me Hooker. I beat
him and then I go to fight for the
title. I beat Hooker and then
>> and then and then wrestling on the RAF.
>> You headbutt it. You headbutted him. But
Dana didn't like that. He doesn't, you
know, there's certain things he wants.
Uh,
>> so Are you Are you Do you have a
relationship with Connor?
>> No.
>> Have you guys ever met?
>> Uh, yeah. I fought on the same card as
uh
I fought the same card as uh Connor.
Connor with Donna is good. Hhabib is
good. Not like all fighters bad with was
done. A lot of fighter like good with
only maybe Jon Jones. Who else and the
the the now Ronda
>> meaning not good with UFC.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But Connor was a little bit
difficult at times. you know, counter,
you know, he gave him a little bit of a
hard time with, you know, throwing that
thing through the glass in the bus,
>> but it's good for the for the
>> Yes.
>> You think they didn't like it? They like
it.
>> So, are you thinking about throwing
something through that window? You're
like, "Let me go
>> grab the chair right now."
>> Yeah. So the the the drama the the sport
or why they this sport is like getting
big because of drama not because of
fighting like Connor Habib
Diaz
you know the trash talk everything not
just fighting what was going on before
the fight
the B thing it was like it went viral
too it was uh
>> was everywhere yeah
>> because of that that that fight was the
mo most fight in uh in the in the UFC.
>> If it wasn't that conflict before that,
>> okay, Conor Habib. Yeah, they talk
in the press conference and they fight,
it's it's gone.
>> Yeah, I saw what you said once. I
thought it was so funny. You said to to
Taporia, correct me if I'm wrong here. I
think you said, I'll buy your house if
you fight me. Did you say something like
that? I'll buy your $3.5 million house
if you fight me.
>> Yeah. Um
so he was selling his house, right? and
he didn't have a fight and I said,
"Yeah, I'll buy his house." And uh and
uh
>> I mean, this is just trolling at its
best.
>> I'll buy your house if you agree to
fight me next. Ilia Tupor has put his $3
half million home for sale.
>> And my dad called me and I heard you're
buying the house in Spain. I said,
"Yeah, when?" He said, "When we going to
vacation?"
>> Your dad said that?
>> Yeah. But who I'm going to call when
he's he's going to say yes.
>> Yeah. Did he did he respond back to you
or No,
>> no. Uh,
>> go a little bit down on the comment
section. Rob Arman, uh, arriving in
Madrid to buy Ilia's house.
>> Yeah, people
>> people are funny with you. Yeah. Um,
that's interesting. So, h how how much
of how much of
matching cuz right now some people would
say the UFC, they've had some good
fights. Like I was at this last one. No
big names. It was actually very good
card. Like if you were at the fight, it
was phenomenal. Probably the best
heavyweight fight that took place that
went the distance. You know the the last
fight where you know he is I don't know
if he was ACL was torn or his you know
>> and he kept getting kicked kick. It's
like this is over with and then all of a
sudden boom
>> and everybody was blown away by the
fight the way it ended. But a big card
they haven't had that for a minute.
>> Yeah. But it's hard. People like
expecting like every title fights like
it's going to be drama this that like
and like they didn't sell a lot of like
a perview or what's it called that I
don't know
>> pay-per-view.
>> Yeah.
But uh for example like all bigger star
booked now like Hamzad big fight coming
up Ilia Pereira on the white house and
um
UFC doesn't have so so much stars to put
on the on the on the every card that's
why like uh and the one fight pulled out
too the common event for the title one
versus I don't know who
uh that's why they didn't sell it a lot
of a lot of tickets and u but you see
you never know you see the names they
learn the big names and you come watch
and like the best fight ever right like
you said title the heavyweight fight
>> so that's why
that's why every every event they they
they have something special matchmakers
works works good so
>> you said you're a fan so if you're a fan
and you everywhere you go people are
talking to you. They want to speak to
you about UFC or different things. If
you could make three fights happen and
you're a matchmaker, who do you create?
What what fights would you want to see
in the UFC?
>> In the UFC?
>> Mhm.
>> Jones versus Pereira.
>> Jones Pereira.
>> Arman versus Gage. Oh, I remember Arman
versus Ilia.
>> Okay.
>> And the next one, Hamza Chim versus Sean
Strickland.
>> Strickland. Those three fights.
>> Yeah. Strickland has a fight that
>> Yeah. versus Hamza.
>> Yeah.
>> And then Pereira John Jones is a big
fight. They wanted to do that fight on
the White House, I guess.
>> But I think John asked for like 30
million or I don't know what the number
was 15 million and they didn't want to
do it. I read somewhere maybe John asked
for a bigger number and they said no,
we're not going to pay it. So it went to
went a different direction.
>> Yeah. In UC a lot of fights you can do.
You can do a lot of fights. Uh 145 is
>> Jones wanted over 15 million. Yeah,
that's what it
>> Jones wanted 15 million for the bout and
it failed due to a reported gap of 5
million. Now, keep in mind this is, you
know, ESPN reporting.
>> Yeah. But I think UC could pay him 15
million.
>> 50 million.
>> 15
>> 15 million.
>> Yeah. Easy for White House. He deserve
it. 15. And I think they they could pay
him. It's it's something like a
different issue.
It's my opinion.
child pella.
>> Okay. So, no chance at all.
>> No chance. Yeah.
>> You know, this whole thing with VIN and
PBD podcast started with a phone, me and
Mario. That's it. And it grew today to,
you know, 15 million subscribers almost
and 164 full-time employees. And that
relationship or you watching us and
supporting us wouldn't happen without
you. But did you know 51% of you that
watch the content are not subscribe to
the channel? And it would mean the world
to us if you could press that subscribe
button and notification. Why? It allows
us to grow, hire more, do bigger
interviews, have a bigger team, and
deliver a better product to you. So, if
you haven't yet, if you don't mind,
press that subscribe button.
>> I think like one of the biggest biggest
event ever, and you think they're not
going to pay 15 million. For sure, they
paid.
>> Yeah,
>> they got a lot of money. So,
>> they got a lot of money. I mean, if you
you
>> and he has not a lot of fights left. So
maybe one two fights John Jones and he's
a legend and like Connor he he made like
15 20 millions right for the fights.
>> Can you pull up what are Conor's highest
you know?
>> No the on the boxing he made a lot but
on the boxing he made in UFC he made I
think for the perview something like 30
mil 20 something million.
>> So not the UFC but on the including
bonuses 5 to6 million bucks is UFC 100
million. Are you sure it's only 5 to six
million bucks the most he made? Can you
ask the same question on chatbt rap
>> and and
>> No, but you never know. Maybe they pay
him extra
>> conversation side. Yeah,
>> but but to me
>> extra bonuses always send me extra
bonuses. Yeah, a couple days ago they
send me 42k. I don't know for what.
Maybe for my for my social media.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. They
>> do. You ever explain where it's coming
from or No,
>> I didn't ask. They
>> You just took the money out.
>> Maybe maybe my manager going to say,
"Hey, where's my person?" I was I was
not saying.
>> So Eddie Alvarez 6.8 million.
Interesting that Eddie's what did he get
paid on Kabib? No way. It was a $3
million flat fight.
>> Was Habib?
>> There is no way it was only 3 million.
>> McGregor claimed it was worth around 50
million total with pay-per-view. Dustin,
they got 5 million a piece. What what is
the highest paid a UFC fighter got paid?
What is the highest?
>> You never going to know because they
used to pay the the the
not on the
>> books?
>> On the books. Yeah. I heard they they
pay so much money when it was fertis.
>> Yeah. I I um I is UFC a publicly traded
company now where they have to report.
Okay. Zoom in on that one a little bit.
Where's the biggest payday total
earnings? But is that earnings to the
fighter or is that earnings to UFC?
>> They say that that's all three fights
combined between
>> No, but I I heard he makes around 20
million the corner
>> a fight.
>> Yeah. From the Habib's fight, he made
like 20 or 30 million.
>> 20 or 30 million.
>> It's good money now.
>> Yeah. But if you look at the most
There's a I think four out of the five
highest uh uh pay-per-view tickets ever
sold, four out of the five counters in
those fights. If you go to the highest
is this go to the highest
UFC pay-per-view ticket sold.
Highest UFC pay-per-view ticket sold.
I want to know top five fights. I think
four out of five
Connor's in all of them.
Okay, zoom in. There you go. Four out of
Actually, five out of five is Connor.
Isn't that amazing? 2.4 million. Damn.
1.8 million. Pier three 1.6 million per
year two 1.6 million Diaz two 1.3
million Diaz one
>> can imagine 2.4 on how much is the per
100 150
>> 70 bucks I don't know what it is I want
to say it's probably 7000 bucks so it's
200 car million
>> damn 80 bucks 80 bucks times 2.4 4
million. That's a That's $200 million
right there.
>> Yeah. Probably he makes around 30 mil
>> on those fights.
>> Hhabib maybe 10 15 and he make probably
about 30 mil.
>> How much you think it's fighting? How
much you think it's his personality and
ability to promote?
>> Uh fighting is uh 80% 70% and 30% is
promote. Like
>> you think that's what it is?
>> Yeah.
>> So okay. So you put 70 of it on a skill
set, 30 of it on the promoting side.
>> Yeah. If you're if you're if you're bad,
you're not you're not going to be in the
title.
>> Interesting. 7030. That makes sense.
>> Yeah. You got to be a good fighter.
Fight for the title.
>> Yeah, that's a very good point.
>> Unless if you're not Patty Pimlet. Penny
Petty Pimlet 10% fighting, 90% uh uh
trash talk. And uh
>> so you think 10% Patty's a pretty good
fighter? He's a He's pretty
>> Did you watch his last fight?
>> Yeah, that was not good. But the
previous one, you know,
>> versus who?
>> Well, I've been I've been to quite a
few. Yeah, he he beat like a trash
canes. He beat he beat they just give
him so easy fights that even my dad can
beat him. Yeah. Really? He beat like a
Tony Ferguson who has nine losing
streak. He beat he beat the
uh what's the
>> just put up his last fights, Rob. Go
down a little bit. It'll show his
fights.
>> Ch Michael Chandler.
>> Michael Chandler. Michael Chandler 10
fights in UFC, nine losses.
>> Is that that's not Michael?
>> Approximately. Approximately click on
Chandler's record.
>> No, King Green. King Green. Check. King
Green.
>> Go on. King Green run.
>> King Green brother. Check his uh last 15
or 10 fights in UFC. Okay. Last 10
fights
go down
>> three.
>> Like five loses, five wins or maybe even
lose.
>> Go to Chandler.
>> I think Chandler. Chandler is like,
>> of course,
>> the thing with Chandler is he's one of
the most ex
>> Chandler's first round may be the most
exciting round in the first round. If
you can make it past the first round,
>> but you're going to have a lot of pain.
>> Yeah.
>> Last one, two, three, four, five. Last
six fights, five losers.
>> Arman, respectfully, he almost beat
Charles. He almost beat Justin. I almost
was a UFC champion.
But these were these were pretty good
fights that he had. I'm telling you his
and if you look at the two rounds, three
rounds, two rounds, three rounds, five
rounds, five rounds with Charles. Yeah,
he's um
he's a
>> last six fights, five losses. That's
crazy.
>> He's a He's a pretty He's a pretty fun
guy to watch.
>> Yeah,
>> he's a pretty fun guy to watch.
>> Like a fan. Yeah. Like first round is
good. his fight versus Gi Tapora or
Porier was good. I mean for fans it's
good to watch but like a fighter
it's hard.
>> You don't you don't think what what's
today is what Rob? April 20
>> 20th.
>> April 20th today. 420 today. Okay. So
and and the White House card is when?
>> June 16th I think.
>> June 16th. So two months till the White
House card.
>> Yeah.
>> I'm sorry. June 14th. You think there is
a 0% chance Dana's going to make an
announcement with a Trump uh with a new
fight?
>> If you call Trump and tell Put Armon on
the card and he's fighting for the US
and maybe they make it,
>> you got to that's the strategy right
there.
>> You got to call Trump and say this guy
is the biggest star right now in
Armenian community and oh my god he
wants he wants uh represent us. Let me
ask you, here's a question. Serious
question. If, god forbid, something
happens to Justin, by the way, when I
was at the fight, Justin spoke to the
president for 10 minutes. They were
standing talking to So, he's a fan. They
have a relationship and he's American.
So,
but if
something happens, Justin's not going.
They put you in, can I say no?
>> No, he cannot say no.
>> Okay. because uh it's a it's a white
house and uh if there are not going to
be other names who is going to be ready
they cannot put anybody but you see
there is a two guys in the 155 division
there is a Chandler
>> but can imagine if they're going to say
to me no and put Chandler fight for the
title
>> oh the audience would be so pissed off
>> that's going to be the worst
they would not be happy
>> or Ruffy I don't know
>> well let me ask you deep down aside
don't you think he wants to see that
fight you against
>> the now they want to see that
>> you don't think Dana wants to see that
fight
>> right now Dana wants
>> why are you saying right now
>> because uh they can see what I'm doing
on my social media on my wrestling
everything I'm just uh
>> bringing a lot a lot of numbers and I
post the April April 1st uh picture me
versus u
>> oh that was
>> and gain more like uh likes and uh the
views than UFC page announced a whole
whole uh whole uh card.
>> Do you see that, Rob? Do you know what
do you know what he's talking about? On
April 1st, he posted that uh uh the
fight is him against Ilia. Did you put
post it on Instagram or or Twitter?
>> Instagram.
>> Go on uh go on his Instagram
>> and go to April 1st.
Where's the card? I don't think you
posted it. There it is right there. 1
million likes.
White House, Washington DC.
This was posted on April 1st.
>> Yeah.
>> This just tells you people want to see
this fight.
>> They're going to see that. They're going
to see this fight. It's going to be one
of the biggest fight. And uh I'm so
excited for that fight, too. I'm just
working every day on that. And they they
think I'm I'm doing this content, but I
train less. But I was training and
getting better. It's just show people
that I'm chilling.
>> Yeah. Is that is that uh is that Nina?
>> Yeah.
>> So, what's the story with you guys? Are
you guys dating or you guys?
>> No. Nina and me, we're the best friends.
She's uh
>> nothing. There's nothing in between and
nothing happened because uh we respect
each other, you know, and u
so we just create the content.
>> There's chemistry there though, bro.
Like that's, you know, like when people
watch you guys, there's a
>> I just want to say one thing. If you if
you if you do with something like uh
you're not going to post anything. If
you have something between you, you're
not going to post it.
Yeah. So, you don't you're not going to
show that who you're dating or like
>> show.
>> Yeah. This show this just the content we
do together and she has a boyfriend. So,
and uh
>> it's amazing. Are you surprised by how
well it performs?
>> Because the her boyfriend he create the
videos and uh he always with her which
is
>> Wait, when you guys do the videos, your
boyfriend's always there.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And is he a fighter as well or No,
>> no, he's a content creator. He does
every videos and like he's so smart and
um he does a lot of social media for
her. They work together. They work
together and like
>> Wow. And
>> this is him.
>> Yeah. So, he's a
>> he's a good-looking guy. I didn't know
this. So, I I thought she was single.
>> No, no, no, she's not single.
>> Is she Is this her husband or her
boyfriend?
>> Boyfriend.
>> Okay. All right.
>> So,
>> and he's doing the content.
>> Yeah, we are like my team and her team
and he's always on her team and he helps
her with the everything.
>> Did you say earlier you have kids or you
don't have?
>> Yeah, I I don't I don't have two kids.
>> You have two kids?
>> Yeah, two kids.
>> So, are you married or
>> I'm married? Married.
>> You are married?
>> Yeah. Got So my my youngest youngest
daughter, she she's like a fighter, but
the older older one, she's like she
doesn't like fights, anything.
>> Two girls.
>> Yeah. Maybe the young young one is going
to be a a fighter.
>> And Arman, are you you're married to an
Armenian?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> To an Armenian from where you're at?
>> Yeah.
>> Very cool. Yeah. That was my mom's
dream. My mom's dream was uh you know,
my son is going to marry an Armenian.
>> Yeah. But doesn't matter if you find the
find right person. Who cares? Armenian,
American, I agree.
>> Black, white, Chinese. So
>> I is two enough for you or are you going
to keep making babies?
>> I can't say we have 11 kids.
>> 11 kids. That's the goal.
>> Yeah.
>> Arman, do are you a Christian or you
you're a Christian?
>> Yeah.
>> Got it. Yeah.
>> You you are thinking like to gain three
more wives. Well, you can speed it up
because you know if there's certain
markets that you can accelerate that
process, you know. I don't know if uh
>> No, nowadays you can do the the thing
what's that called? The
>> surrogate.
>> Surrogate. Yeah.
>> Yeah. What do you think about that?
>> I think it's okay.
>> Would you would you entertain it
>> if you want more kids? Yeah.
>> I brought it up to my kids. My my
youngest son is like, "You can never
have surrogate." I said, "Why?" I said,
"It's your mommy and daddy's. It's your
brother or sister. He says, "No, no, if
it's not in my mom's stomach."
>> No way.
>> He I'm telling you, he told me,
>> "No." By the way, he he is he looks
Armenian.
His mom's white Texan, but Dylan looks
Armenian and he has the Armenian temper
and blood.
>> Well, he is.
>> Well, he's going to be a fighter, huh?
>> We'll see what he does. Right now, he
plays uh he plays uh he's the one to the
left. Yeah,
>> he plays soccer and he does some other
sports, but we'll see. We'll see what's
going to happen with him. By the way,
did you ever train with any Armenian
fighters? Like, are you did you train
with other Armenian UFC fighters?
>> Yeah, I trained to Melik uh Edmund
Shaan. Yeah. So, but um they're in
different weight class. That's why we
don't train together. And uh
they cannot keep up with me.
>> Who's going to keep up with you today
though?
>> Yeah, that's hard. So, uh, but
you see me and Hamza, we like we do
together and like when we in the gym
always argue who does this better, who
does this better? So, but I'm the number
one on the bike. You cannot break my
record.
>> You're the number one on the bike.
>> Yeah.
>> In bike, what? What's number one? Like,
who can go to fastest longest?
>> Who can like keep more watts on the
bike? I'm number one from garage. So,
put the garage thing. Yeah. Yeah. This
one. So in this bike from fighters,
nobody can beat me. Other thing and this
thing for the shoulders. Yeah. So two of
those uh nobody
but other thing like a running speed
running or like
I don't know
>> what an exercise. So they drop the ball
while you're carrying the weight as
well. You're pushing up the weight.
>> Yeah. This is coach call and he has his
own garage. He doesn't like fancy
things. We just go there and train train
hard. So, and he push ourselves so much.
So, when I want to want to when I'm at
home, I want to try to break the record.
I cannot because he's not there. I I got
to listen his voice and like he's like
trying to push me so much. You cannot
like
>> Is he your coach or is he his coach?
>> It's my coach. And then when he came and
he trained with him and he like it. So,
yeah. So, uh good coach.
But um
but he has his own coaches too with him
like a jiu-jitsu and boxing.
>> Yeah. What's what's with you with you
doing the life that you're living right
now? What's how much is the expense on a
monthly basis? How much money are you
spending
>> in one place? I said 500,000 but it was
wrong.
>> Was it more or less?
>> My dad called me after that where you
spent 500,000.
Now I got to say 100,000. You got to
tell them 100,000.
>> Yeah. I mean, so I have a big team,
right? I have a big team. I have a
I have a coaches. I have like a
lifestyle family. If you We're buying
like a
vort, we're buying houses, we're buying
cars, if you're going to if you're going
to like count everything, it's going to
be 500,000
>> per month. Yeah. All So your lifestyle
expense right now is 6 million a year
>> about. And is your fighting income and
sponsorship paying for that lifestyle or
not yet?
>> About? Yeah.
>> So about
>> Yeah. And I have a I have a businesses
in Russia that I make money. Yeah. So
and uh I always have a on my back
Russian money. So if I need it,
>> you have access to that as well.
>> I call it. So
>> yeah, you have access to that as well.
>> Yeah. You know, I grew up there. I live
there. So I know how to make money over
there.
>> What's what's Russia to you? We're in
America. So to us, you know, we, you
know, we we have a different uh, you
know, Americans may have a different
impression of, you know, Russia. What's
Russia to? What makes Russia special for
you?
>> Wherever I go to travel, to stay, you
want to go back to Russia. No matter
here, Miami so beautiful roads, beach,
food, cars, yachts,
but you don't feel like you're at home
and you want to go back to home. My home
is in Russia. I grew up there. I like
nature there. I like
food there. Everything was going on over
there. I like it.
>> Do you see yourself as a Russian or
Armenian?
>> Second. You see you see yourself as
Russian or Armenian
>> citizen?
>> No. Do you see yourself highest
rousas? How?
>> No. No. I'm Armenian.
>> You're Armenian?
>> Yeah, I'm Armenian but I live Russia.
So,
>> and uh where I live in Cresender is like
a lot of a lot of Armenian people like
five about 500,000 Armenian people live.
Uh it's like you Yeah. It's like a
glandal in US. Same over there.
>> Yeah.
>> I got to go to I've never been to it.
>> Yeah. Russia is it's good. It's clean.
It's safe. It's clean. And it's safe.
Um, yeah, if you compare to US, it's
safer and cleaner.
>> Russia.
>> Yeah, Russia.
>> Safer and cleaner.
>> So safe.
>> Tell me why. Safer.
>> So you can wear, you can walk anywhere,
any watches, nobody can come and trying
to grab you.
>> Why is that? Why do you think?
>> Because people is scared to do
something.
>> Why?
>> Because they go to jail right away.
They're not going to sue with you or do
something. If you steal, you go to jail.
And uh and they clean the mafia,
everything. Now it's a it's a so safe
country. And uh I've never heard like
someone scared about watch like for
example here or LA, you cannot go
somewhere with your watches or with your
uh cars. You cannot get in some some
certain places. But in Russia is you can
go anywhere any any places and never
never happened
>> because people are afraid of the
consequences and
>> and because of that and they clean the
bad people too. So they they're in the
jail. So all mafia in the jails now or
like they're abroad of from Russia.
>> Wow.
>> So that's why
I never think like about bodyguard in
Russia or like oh my family cannot go
outside or something. But here like
everybody, every celebrity has a
bodyguards. Every fighters like who has
a big name, they have a bodyguards
and uh people there respect you so much.
Especially if you're fighter, they don't
even come and like try to ask you about
something, get the picture, they just
respect your time, you know,
>> over there,
>> over there. And if they tell them you're
in a rush, so let they let you go. But
here they can be talk to you you know
and like say no no no stop I want a
picture this that and then you need to
someone to say them please he got to go.
So people here they don't afraid that he
they can like get a problem but there
they afraid because you know they they
let you do whatever you want to do. How
>> how do Russians think of Putin? Is it a
high level of respect and admiration?
Yeah, mostly people like him because
they they live there. They they respect
what he's doing. They like him. And uh
So,
>> have you met him yet?
>> Yeah, two times.
>> Really?
>> Yeah, two times. And I was fighting for
his uh for his team. So, we got the
pictures. You can put it. Yeah. So, you
see young me.
>> Oh, wow. How old are you here?
>> 20 years old.
>> Arma, it's a very different look.
>> Yeah, but I was 20 or 19.
And what was this year?
>> It was uh uh 17 or 18.
>> Uh it says 2025 the
>> day. Yeah. So I was I was fighting two
times. He has a his own promotion. It's
once a year. Once a year on the in the
Soi and the Russian fighters versus uh
the world. So they bring all uh fighters
from the world
and uh
and uh yeah they they they fight.
>> Is that Fedor?
>> It's a failure. Yeah.
>> Really?
>> Wow, man. He he still has the Matter of
fact, he looks better now.
>> Yeah, he's he's feed now.
>> Yeah, he looks better now. What What
What did Putin tell you? Was it just a
meeting or did he say anything?
>> I asked her, "Can I take a picture?" She
said, "Of course, of course you take a
picture." And then yeah, he's he's cool
and he likes the fighter. He he helps so
much fighters and wrestlers and
everybody in in Russia. So if you're
wrestler, for example, here government,
they don't pay money to you. But in
Russia, we get paid. If you're like an
Olympic team in your if you're Russian
champion, you get paid money. If you win
once in your life Olympic game, Olympic
medal, you getting paid all your life
until you die.
>> You're serious?
>> Yeah. Yeah, you can check this
information.
>> So you you win one medal, you're getting
paid for the rest of your life.
>> Yeah, like $1,000
>> for the rest of your life.
>> Yeah. But can imagine if you win three
times, you're getting paid three or
4,000
>> every month for the rest of your life.
>> Every month. Yeah. You can check it out.
>> Very interesting business model. So, so
it's not like you're getting paid one
time cuz in America, I think we pay you
one time.
>> One time. And no, America doesn't
doesn't pay even one time. They tell you
you got to find the sponsorship and they
pay
>> the money that way. Huh. But in Russia,
they pay their medalist. So there's an
incentive to win for the rest of your
life.
>> But can you check uh they pay you how
much they pay?
>> Rob, can you check to see go to uh Yeah.
Go and ask and say what does Russia pay
its
uh Olympic athletes if they win a medal?
>> It was like $800. like like I heard one
>> because I have a lot of friends
>> who have won.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Metal. M E D A L. Okay, there you
go.
>> So for recent Beijing, Russia has paid
roughly
50 to $60,000 for gold, 30 to 35 for
silver, 20 to 25 for bronze. Some
broader estimates go a little bit lower.
But here's the real kicker. Russia often
goes above and beyond just cash. Lux
luxury cars, apartments worth half a
million to a million now. Regional
bonuses from local governments, extra
payouts from sports federation,
total rewards can be hundreds of
thousands of dollars to million plus.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah. They uh it's a Olympic sport. They
they take care of them so much. So for
example, if you're a you want to be a
box, you go to school, you don't pay
money. You if you're a wrestler, you go
to school, you don't pay money for the
for the sport. How do they define you
that you have to be at a certain level
of skill set?
>> No. No. If you're a kid, you go to the
school, you don't pay money for for your
sport. In Russia,
>> no matter how old you are,
>> no matter if it's not commercial, there
is like a
every area has his own the government
pay for that school that kids can train
for free. So you go there. So when I was
young, I was I was wrestling, right?
Even government pay me for my traveling.
If I travel to somewhere to compete,
they they paid us money for our travel
even. Yeah. They take care of Olympic
sports so much and they
for example, you're a fighter. You got
even Khabib, he got paid for the for his
gym. I put him uh
built for him a gym. For example, you're
a gold, you want a gold and you want to
build your own gym, they gift you money
to build your own gym
>> if you're a gold medalist.
>> Yeah.
>> So, so Russia, so Putin helped Kabib
build his gym.
>> Yes.
>> That is powerful.
>> Yeah. I mean, they they take care of for
example somewhere you go somewhere in
Russia, if you're a fighter or wrestler
in government or somewhere, they take
care of you because you you do something
for you for for your country. They take
care of you so much. So it's it's the
yeah they take care of you different. So
>> how to know that?
>> I mean in US it's opportunity to make so
much money.
>> It's uh
it's a lot of good things here. A lot of
good things there.
>> Do you get sponsorship money there or
No, it's mainly from the government.
>> Uh in Russia? No, I got
>> So you get sponsorship as well?
>> Yeah, I got the energy drink in Russia.
>> In Russia that'll pay you as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So you get a little bit of
both.
>> Yeah.
>> There's long term after UFC. Do do you
know do you have any thoughts of what
you going to do after UFC or
>> depends how much money I make.
>> But uh I want to live I want to have a
house in like I want to live in Russia
my home base but I want to travel around
the world. come to US, enjoy Miami and
then from Miami to LA, from LA to New
York, from New York to Hawaii and then
go back because the winter time is not
the best weather in Russia, but uh from
May to October is Russia weather.
>> Can you pull up Russia's map, Rob? Just
curious to know what part you're from.
>> Go to the Soi.
I I want to show the our the
>> Yeah, right there. the mountains that we
to uh we ski we do snowmobile everything
over there. So where here this is so
>> go to go to the crash palana. Uh this is
the Soi this is the the biggest this is
the the sea.
So this is the mountains. Uh can you put
the Soi mountains?
It's beautiful.
Just the pictures pictures pictures.
Yeah. From the browser. Yeah. Yeah.
Check it out.
>> Better than Oh my god. Click on that
picture. right there, Rob. The the first
one. Zoom in on that picture.
>> So beautiful.
>> Wow.
>> Yeah.
I mean, when you stay in Russia long
time, you want to leave from there, too.
You want to go somewhere, travel, and
then come back.
>> Totally makes sense.
>> Yeah.
>> But we're never going to get you in the
US. You're never going to be living
here. You're always going to go back to
Russia.
>> I mean, I like to be here from November.
>> From May to November.
>> November, December, January, February,
March.
and April maybe. Yeah. Six months here,
six months there.
>> May to November there and then the rest
over here because the weather.
>> Yeah.
>> And your home here. You were telling me
you were saying you
>> LA. LA. When I landed to LA, I feel like
you I'm in Russia as well. Armenia.
Yeah. Russia because when I'm in
Armenia, I cannot stay long long time
there. Everybody knows me. It's hard.
>> I got to go. Have you met the prime
minister of Armenia yet, Pashinan? Or
no? Have they ever reached out to you
or?
>> No.
>> Never.
>> Never. some would you want to go uh you
know meet him or
>> I mean I I did so much for this country
of course I would like to
>> I'm surprised they've never reached out
>> to them to do something because uh
>> I'll make one phone call
>> they they never done it something for me
you know like they at least maybe give
me a small medal that I'm doing there
and putting the flag on my shoulders and
like running out in whole US you know
>> oh they're going to reach out to you.
There's no way in the world if you got a
guy like you that you're doing what
you're doing.
>> For sure. For sure. For sure they know
about me. But
>> of course they know about
>> I don't need their help. But if they go
if they want to help me, I'll be glad,
you know.
>> Yeah. I I I think if you uh uh if you
were to go visit,
>> but Armenians from Russia, they help me.
So Armenians from Russia, the uh they
help me a lot.
>> How do you view the difference? Yeti.
No. No, I'm saying that because my
friends from Russia who is in business,
they that they help me. They give me
houses, they give me apartments. So,
yeah.
>> Armon, question for you. Can you like
what what does it mean to be Armenian?
Cuz to me, I'm Armenian and Assyrian,
but what does it mean to be Armenian?
>> For me,
>> yeah,
>> I'm proud to be Armenian.
>> Uh, I'm proud to represent Armenian. I
want to be a first Armenian champion
and uh
so in UFC we don't have like a
contenders like a good fighters who is
going to be a champion very soon but uh
I'm I'm going to sign young kids and I
see the potential so big maybe because
of me because of like the sport is
growing up so fast getting so popular
that's I a lot of kids is training and I
now I have a couple kids who who's like
19 18 and they they if they going to be
in UFC they can be a champion. Yeah.
>> Back in Russia. India.
>> Uh mostly in Russia. Yeah. Mostly in
Russia because in Armenia is not so
popular but uh we got someone from there
too. And u I want to bring the belt. I
want to represent Armenia and be a first
champion because Russia has already a
lot of champions. So
yeah, but anyway, I'll
uh belt
>> first
>> belt first and then I bring to Armenia.
So like
>> Oh my god, that would be a spectacle.
>> Yeah,
>> Arman John, let me tell you, you know,
everybody I speak to in the Armenian
side when they talk about you, you are
beloved. They love you.
>> Thank you.
>> Absolutely love you. And you got, you
know this already, so I don't need to
tell you this. They're rooting for you
and we can't wait for the day. I gota
and I like Ilia. I like Taporia. You
know, there's something very because
both of you guys, what's going to make
this exciting, both people have a lot of
pride from the country they're from.
>> He's got a very interesting dynamic.
It'll be interesting to see how much
animosity there is between Spain and
Russia. I don't know.
>> Spain, Russia, Armenia versus Georgia.
>> That's right. Oh, I was right. I was
born in Georgia. My home like
>> for example, when we go to Armenia,
>> we stay there one day and then drive to
back to Georgia and stay there because
our home in Georgia. So, we'll build new
house now in Georgia and all my family
live there. So, even like
uh we close to Georgia. So now like
Armenia versus Georgia, but I live in
Russia and he lives in Spain and like
they gonna know who is the best fighter
in 155 division because in Russia, yeah,
I'm Armenian, but Russian people,
>> they uh they support me so much too.
They they know I live there. They know
like
I'm going to bring the belt into the
Russian home. You know
>> if if doesn't happen on the White House
card
>> and if your ideal place that you would
want to fight Tuporia where would it be?
>> No matter when no matter where
>> anytime anywhere
>> anytime, anywhere. I just need that
belt. Even not I don't care. you know,
uh, like I just need to be a first get
the belt and then I'm going to get the
this hat, the big hats, so big names.
Uh, because right now for me, it's
number one to be a UFC champion and I
know I know myself. I know my skills. I
can beat them. It's not it's not going
to be big problem for me. Yeah, this is
good side quest. uh the area of
grappling like a media but in the end of
days if they they ask me uh what are you
going to take UFC belt or this old
things so I need just UFC belt because I
wake up and I do this for UFC title too.
I'm not doing this because
like I need that because like make money
from that just that UFC going to uh
going to know that it's big name because
of this media I'm making my my name
bigger and um my goal is UFC. So right
now is is that but then when I become a
UFC champion I'm going to go for the
names and make money because
like you know my
>> lifestyle make money.
>> Yeah it's expensive and thank God I got
money and uh
>> have you thought about starting a
product? Are you working on a product
because
>> not yet I don't want to uh think about
like about business that going to take
my time. So that's why I'm just focusing
only on my uh social media and only on
my trainings because uh when I'm done
when I'm going to be like done with UC
sport when I'm going to be like 37 38
yeah I'm going to do my products or
something. But I think when I'm going to
be 37, I I'm not going to be need
products and then everything. So I'm
going to have a bunch of money, good
investments
and like family man. So enjoy
retirement.
>> Yeah. And you'll be in Russia from May
to November and in LA or Miami or other
places November to April. Maybe April.
You said March. from November, beginning
of the and end of October. Beginning of
November here and and then of March.
>> All right.
>> So, but summer time sometimes in Europe,
too.
>> In Europe, too. It's your favorite spot
>> in Europe.
>> Yeah.
>> To be honest, I like all spots. Yeah. I
like to travel around the Europe.
>> Have you been all over like
>> No, not yet. Not yet. But I've been a
lot of places.
>> Have you been to Monaco yet?
>> Yeah.
>> You've been to Monaco? I'm assuming you
love Monaco?
>> Yeah, for sure.
>> Central Bay was my lifestyle. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's what I'm saying. With your
lifestyle, that's a
>> When you go to Monaco, you realize how
broke you are.
>> Yes.
>> You go to Monaco, you know, you know,
the average net worth of a person living
in Monaco is $30 million.
>> No, I I feel broke every day even
because I have a lot of friends who is
like a uh who has a lot of money when
they talk about money and I talk about
two three millions. Yeah. Like
>> they they laughing at me. So everybody
has his own thing you know that's why so
uh we work on it you know everybody has
his own uh
>> but you have the one skill set that's
very hard armon you have you have a so
you know currency isn't isn't different
you know bitcoin could be a currency
real estate is a currency right stocks
is a currency all this stuff is a
currency getting attention is a currency
and dude you are a master at getting
attention And you do it in the most
effortless way.
>> And and that currency
people pay there's a reason why for
Super Bowl they pay $10 million for a 30
secondond commercial to get in front of
110 million people and you don't have a
problem doing that.
>> Yeah. Um what about Bitcoin?
>> It's at 65 70,000 right now. You know,
if it goes to half a million, that's 8x.
You know, I think if you're making
money,
you gota Rob, it went up 3.4% today.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Really? Interesting.
>> Do you buy bitcoins?
>> I have Bitcoin. I have Bitcoin. I uh you
know, not a lot though. I probably have
less than 5 million in Bitcoin. Uh but
my money is more in equities. I have
probably a 100 million in real estate.
Um,
you know,
>> the best real estate in Russia, by the
way.
>> Best real estate in Russia. Tell me why.
Safety.
>> Safety. And it never fall. So, it's
going up. So, so really Russia real
estate.
>> Yeah.
>> And if you have a friends who de
developers
and they give you good price and you can
make and you can double your money in
one year
>> in Russia.
>> In Russia. So, if you want to make
money, let me know.
we make money there.
>> Let's do it. So, we're going to we're
going to buy property in Russia
together. This means
>> No, no, no. For example, like sorry for
interrupt you. For example, you buy
commercial or house right here, you got
to wait like 20 years. For example, you
buy a commercial for 100,000. Sure. For
example,
>> and you give it to rent, you getting
back your money in 20 20 years here. But
in Russia, you get get back in eight
years. 8 to 10.
>> How is that? You're saying the rate of
return is that good in Russia?
>> Yeah. Better than here because I
calculate everything and uh yeah, their
return is faster and like the price is
growing faster too.
>> Are you investing a lot right now as
well or no?
>> Yeah, invest in mostly in Russia. mostly
in Russia
>> because I know people who developers
>> connections contact
>> I know like where
>> but your dad was also in construction
right so he knows everybody
>> that's why it's easier for example if I
buy something he does everything inside
so we don't waste money
>> and you can't get ripped off cuz you
know that business your dad knows that
business you see that's half the battle
the battle is the average person that
gets into an industry it takes three
five years you know seven years of
making mistakes and then you make money.
>> Yeah.
>> But if you can get into a space that you
already have the context, the
relationship, and somebody can teach you
to not make the mistakes, there's nobody
better than a dad to share that with
you. I can't wait to meet your dad. I'm
actually curious to know what his
personality.
>> He needs a he needs a American visa. He
doesn't he cannot get it get the
American visa. Five times he was in the
embassy. Five times he didn't give him.
I don't know why
he he's not terrorist.
So
>> five times he tried to get it, they
didn't give it to you.
>> Yeah. But uh he's uh maybe they ask him
question and he's like a worry, you
know, that he wants to get the American
visa so much. That's why he worry and
they think like uh he has something to
hide, you know.
>> I think when you become a champion,
you're going to be able to do a lot of
things you want to do.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And it'll be a phone call.
>> Yeah. But it's not it's okay me to be a
champion. He's going to be good in rush,
I think. So just just bring their belt
to and give it to him. He's going to be
epic too. Yeah. But I want He likes us.
I don't know why. People who never been
in US, they like more than who is in US.
Everybody wants to come here.
>> It's true.
>> It's true. Yeah. It's a It's a a land of
opportunity. Yeah.
>> Because you can like
>> create something and like you can
>> What's different? You you go you're in
Russia all the time.
>> Yeah. Because in Russia less people less
money.
>> People has no so much money. Like here
for example, you open the restaurant
right
>> here. so much um people coming tourists
a lot of people live here and they you
you're going to have customers and the
the for example in Russia if you're
smart
uh the uh the millionaires and
billionaires less in Russia because
uh
it's it's it's hard to how do you say
for example here you have a lot of
opportunities so much
>> in Russia if you're smart,
you you you you can make more money than
here. But here, like for example, you
came from Russia, you have nothing and
you're not the smartest person ever, you
can even go to Uber, you you make money
six or 7,000 and you can afford the
house for your family and food. But in
Russia, if you're like a Uber driver,
you cannot afford. You got to do
something different
>> because of people.
>> Because of people. So for example they
don't have so people don't have so much
money like here they have money the
salary average of sal sal sal sal sal
sal sal sal sal sal sal sal sal sal sal
sal sal sal sal sal salary in US is
bigger than in Russia.
>> Mhm.
And here a lot of tourists so much
tourists LA a lot of tourists can how
many flights is landing in
>> you don't have it Russia doesn't have a
lot of tourists
>> not so much like here
>> because the weather maybe because the
weather
>> weather and visas I think and like uh
they don't have so much thing like US
has you know from movies everybody wants
to come to go to New York to see New
York Miami every movie is from Miami
everybody has a dream to come to see
ocean um the ocean driver was called
that because of movies.
>> M
>> everything is coming from here and like
people
>> what a way I mean it's crazy because
when I was in Iran we watch movies about
here so every Rocky oh my god I want to
go see what you know New York is looking
like you know all this stuff and the
movie industry almost promoted and sold
America to the world.
>> Yes. Everybody wants to come from movie
New York. If you're going to ask every
girl in Russia, where you want to go? I
want to go to New York. And they don't
know like maybe it's not the cleanest
city in the world. It's not the the
safest city in the world, but everybody
wants to go there.
>> Yeah.
>> And that's why they bring a lot of
tourists here.
>> Well, a lot of men here want to go to
Russia, find a wife, and come back here
because Russia's got some beautiful
women over there.
>> Yeah. One of the best.
>> One of the best. Great genetics.
>> Yeah. So you got to come Russia.
>> I look forward to it. I really want to
go to Russia like
>> and then and then you going to you're
going to see what's the different from
Russia. And
>> where do I go if I go there? Like if you
tell me two places to visit. Of course I
I I think I got to go to Moscow.
Lenningrad.
>> Yeah. Yeah. The places. And then you
come to Soi. We go to mountain.
>> Okay.
>> We eat the we eat good food.
>> Was that food video on Sochi? The
snowboarding.
>> No, it's one it was in Kushville.
>> It was in Kushville.
>> Yeah. Got it. Yeah. I really want to go
to Russia for a couple of weeks.
>> Yeah. You will love Russia. You will
love it. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, I have a
friends who who lives all his life in
US, but they come to Armenia and they
want to go or Russia. They want to go
back because they grew up here. They
love they live there.
>> Should I worry like should my wife be
worried that if I go to Russia, maybe I
don't come back?
>> Or will I come back? I will
>> come back, but maybe not alone. Okay.
You're so
>> And we're not going to tell.
>> My wife's going to be like, "Babe, why
are you going to Russia so often?" All
of a sudden, Rob, we're setting up a
podcast set in Russia where there's six
months out of the year,
>> business changes, lifestyle changes.
>> Yeah. But everywhere is good. Everywhere
is good if you have a right people.
And uh so I'm in US, nobody
like
>> Do they treat you good when you're in
the streets here? Does anybody bother
you? They're all respectful.
>> So good. Respectful. And uh yeah, for
example, yesterday I was sitting on the
table and like one drunk guy came and
like trying to like like uh like he did
like this like a
>> squeezing your squeezing. I'm like his
kid, you know. And uh that day, I don't
know why my friends gave me like
bodyguard,
>> but I don't need bodyguard, right? So he
squeezed me and like I turned like he
was like Albanian guy you know bro I
respect you this that I said bro like if
you respect me why you like treat me
like your kid sorry I was drunk this he
was a good guy so he said sorry this
that but can you imagine if the he was
starting like why you saying that and
like and then we so when I like turn and
the bodyguard say I was already angry
like if why you like treat me like this
I'm not your kid like come and like
squeeze my uh the shoulder or what
whatever Yeah.
>> Don't do that. If you respect me, right?
>> You told them that.
>> Yeah. And I said, "If you respect me,
don't do that."
>> Albanians are tough. Albanians are also
tough.
>> Yeah. But
>> I mean, in US, you can meet everybody.
So, you know what I'm saying? Like,
>> has anybody tried to fight you or No,
>> at all. Has there ever been a time where
you travel and someone tried to fight
you?
>> No. No. So, no yet. Maybe. But if they
want to fight me, it's not a problem.
I can I know how to fight, not get hurt
myself. So,
>> no, I think it's a bad idea. That's the
thing, you know, sometimes where you go
and and one time, do you remember Diego
Sanchez? Old UFC fighter. Yeah.
>> Used to go, "Yes, yes, yes." He was one
of my favorite fighters. One day, uh uh
one of our friends, he goes to a party
at a house in uh LA, and he has no clue
who he is. And my friend's a regular
guy. He's not like a tough guy. He's not
a fighter, but he's a big guy. He walks
up to him and says something to him. And
Diego looks at him. He says, "You say
one more thing, I'm going to kill you."
And Diego looked scary, right? When when
he was fighting, he comes back around.
He's like, "I'm going to go kick that
guy's ass." And then one of Diego's
people walks over and says, "Listen,
just want to let you know that's the
wrong guy to fight. That's Diego
Sanchez."
>> Yeah.
>> He looks him up. the the the the
challenge is you pick on sometimes the
wrong guys who know how to fight. Who
knows what could happen. And nowadays,
you know, Arman, more and more people
are learning how to fight. 30 years ago
in LA, people would fight all the time.
You don't know who you were fighting.
So, at least two people who don't know
how to fight, they're fighting. They
just have a temper. Now, there are more
people who know how to fight today than
30 years ago.
>> Yeah, for sure. But, you know,
all time something happened, right? you
I meet every day some different people I
can feel like you know for example if
they tell me like even bad words I just
turn and go if he's not a fighter or
he's not like a if he didn't like do
something to me
>> why do you do that why do you walk away
>> because I don't need the trouble first
of all I don't want to hurt him I don't
I have like a goal I have a family I'm
not stupid like go to jail and I can
>> every day something happen with me
because right now I'm a famous and like
a lot of people come do this that like
for example in Russia if someone come
and squeeze me and if my friends see
that they going to like fight him right
away or just like a like different they
it that's because of they can fight him
they not going to do that because they
afraid they not like come and touch
someone like even like a a fighter how
you can come
>> if you respect him like touch like this
>> in Russia that won't happen
>> it won't happen because they Oh, they
going to kicked out from this place even
>> if you do. By the way, what happened
with Ryan Garcia? You had your friend
with you and he said, "Hey, punch him in
the stomach for $40,000."
>> No, he has a 40,000 with him.
>> Okay.
>> He said, "Uh, he wanted to punch Ashton
Hull." Ashton Hull, the the guy who is
running
>> the runner. Yes.
>> And Ashton has said no. I said, "Bro,
like 40,000 for me it's nothing. Double
it. I'll take three punches." He said,
"No, I don't I'm not rich like you this,
that." I said, "Okay, here's my friend.
You want to punch him?" He said, "Yes,
let's do it." And he put money on the
strayers. I said, "Bro, I don't have
cash with me. I'll show I'll show him my
bank account that I have 30 uh uh 40k
there." I said, "I'll leave my phone
here. When we done, if he he if you if
you could hit him, hurt him, and he's
going to drop, I'll wire you right
away." Because in my culture if you
shake the hand and like we bet you got
to give back money you cannot like say.
>> So he punch it three times he couldn't
drop him and I took the money and the
his accounter or whatever came and said
bro here is more than 40,000 let me go
upstairs like count money and then come
back. I said okay.
He came back without money. I said
where's the money? No no no bro we we
wire you. We need this money for
tonight. we do something. I said,
"Brian, no. I need now my money." He
said, "Bro, I swear to God, uh, like a
man word, I'm going to give you I'm
going to wire tomorrow." One week,
nothing.
And my I was in I was uh I was someone
like interviewed me. Did you get paid
back? I said, "No, he didn't send me
money." And he didn't
>> You never got the money.
>> Yeah. And he didn't even like call me
what's your wire or why I'm not sending
and I FaceTime you. I facetimed him and
I said, "Bro, like what's going on?"
"Bro, you didn't tell me your guy is
professional boxer." I said, "Why I
should tell you like he's a professional
boxer? He's my" I said, "This is my
friend. If you want to punch him, punch
him." I'm not stupid like to say you
like, "Oh, listen. He's professional
fighter. He's going to take your shots
and I'm I'm not going to bet. I'm I'm
going to bet."
>> So, he thought you hustled him.
>> Yeah. So, I'm a smart guy. Like, I want
to bet and make money, right?
So, why I should tell him he's a
professional boxer and you see he's like
a huge guy with a broken nose. You got
to you got to you got to think like he's
Yeah, he's he do he does something and
then he fought with him. He did the
boxing uh the sparring with him on the
body shop
>> when
>> the same day and he didn't say this
guy's professional world. He didn't say
anything.
>> Oh, so before this they sparred?
>> No, after this they sparred.
>> Okay. So, you want to show the Is this
the punch? Let me see it real quick. Let
me see it real quick. prop.
>> No, not there. It's going to be right
here.
>> He knows the point that he can't hit.
>> I know. He knows.
>> Come on.
>> I don't think I can do this.
>> I would have felt he he failed it that
he's not going to drop him because he's
a boxer. He He felt it. He's not going
to drop him with was with was with was
with was with was with was with was with
was with was with was with was with was
with was with with his one punch and he
has two left and he stop it and he's
saying I don't want to hurt him because
he already know he's not going to drop
him. Listen what he's saying.
>> Okay. I I rather spar rather spar
>> now he wants to spar because
>> you take it brother. I'm rather spar
him.
>> Yeah. You take it, brother.
>> Let a man try to hit me.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah, you guys got it.
>> Yeah, we got it.
>> Wait. He took the cash. Then this guy
comes takes him from you and you never
got
>> no and then I said no it's not fair that
punch him two times again
>> let's do it I rather I rather fight
>> yeah yeah
>> oh no they no they he throw three times
he couldn't he couldn't drop him
>> no hell no
>> they did
>> do good doing business with you brother
>> one second
>> sad face for me
in me pocket
So, and then they sparred,
>> but uh to be honest, I don't care about
40k. Just uh
>> so you never got the money.
>> No, no. And then I call him and said,
"Bro, like what's going on? Why you
didn't say money?" Bro, it he said,
"Bro, it was a stream, so we always do
on the stream like this." And don't I
say, "Okay." So, what I'm going to say
to him, we have a different culture.
They do stream and they do um
>> Yeah, but you're a serious guy.
>> Yeah, they live like this. I live
different. And then he said, "Let's
let's do sparring. Let's do eight rounds
this that." I said, "Okay, let's do
sparring, but box, but let me use my
elbows." He said, "No problem." So, now
we're waiting. Uh we're going to do a
sparring. So, I can box him. He can, but
I have elbows.
>> You're not worried about if you box him
against Ryan?
>> No.
>> So, you can't kick or wrestle? It's just
boxing except you can use elbows.
>> Yeah, I can use elbow.
>> And you think you're going to hang with
Ryan?
>> Yeah, I'm going to try.
>> Ryan's a Ryan.
>> Yeah, he's a legit the wrestler.
>> Oh, there's no question.
>> Elbows could help me, too.
>> Elbows could help you. He's uh
>> he never he never he
elbows there is nothing.
>> Yeah,
>> it's nothing.
>> even
>> Oh, it hits the face. He's
>> Yeah. One cut. That's it.
>> Yeah.
>> So, and then he uh
>> now you got to get indoor, right? We got
to get him cuz he's got the reach.
>> And now he's saying he he tweet he he
after that conversation he tweet let's
do eight rounds I'll pay you 100k. So
eight rounds and I I tweet him back I'll
give you cash 1 million if you survive
one round in a so now she's waiting just
waiting but it's just trash talking you
know.
>> Yeah. So
>> and he's good at it as well. He is
>> he's good on on his thing. I'm good on
my thing. So totally
>> both of you guys get eyeballs. You know,
at one point he was the guy in the
boxing time and and I hope he gets back
into it because he's actually a very
exciting fighter.
>> Yeah,
>> he's a very exciting fighter.
>> Fast. So
>> yeah, he's he is very rare you.
>> But now I know if I'm going to do a
stream with him, I'm not going to the
bad money.
>> Or if you do, take the money and don't
give it to his accountant when he comes
up to you.
>> First time in my life uh someone like
You say stuff like this, if an Armenian
sees him in the streets, you don't want
the Armenians to go after him and say,
"Hey."
>> No. I told
No, no. I told Hamza, he said, "4k,
>> I'll go for for 40k to his house."
>> I said, "Bro, like, please do your
thing.
>> Leave him alone."
>> And then we figure out. So, yeah. But,
uh, we'll see. When we see him, we talk
to him and, uh, we figure out. Maybe we
do some different bad.
>> Yeah.
>> But but it's, you know, it's always
>> But listen,
>> but but I have a bad with Aiden Rose.
Hamzad versus uh Hamzad versus um I put
50K on Hamzad. He put 50K on uh uh
Strickland. So, and I told him 5050.
>> Yeah. I told him
>> he put 50 Strickland again. Hamza,
>> I wanted to put like 1 million. He said
like 100. He said 50. 50. I said okay
50. He put against Hamzad, he put 50.
Yeah, it's a tough fight. You never
know. Even Even Hamzad, my friend, he's
my brother. But, uh, you never know.
It's a fight. And second, Strickland is
tough. Tough a tough fighter. So, he has
a lot of uh a lot of good things, you
know.
>> When is it? When is it? Is it in May?
>> May 9th.
>> Yeah. So, but I told Aiden Rose,
"Brother, fly out with So, I uh fly out
with money over there. Cash." And I'm
going to bring cash as well.
>> Is that GSP sitting next to you?
>> Yeah. Legend.
>> He's like one of the nicest
>> Yeah.
>> legends of all time.
>> He He was with a streamer with me, you
know, like GSP
like he was in the zoo with us.
>> Yeah.
>> He got in the zoo with us.
>> And that's not his style. He's not that
guy. He's a He's a lowkey guy.
>> But when he was with us, we were like
good, you know, like respectful. When he
was gone and like we started like
talking
>> Yeah. He is truly a class act.
>> Yeah.
>> He's a class act.
>> Different level.
>> Strickland, you know, Strickland is a
guy that
Do did you did you see the clip that one
time where a guy came in to try to rob
him or do have you seen that clip
>> with the gun? He came came out with the
gun and the
>> Yeah. And he just I don't remember what
I
>> No, he's he's really like this.
>> Oh, he
>> he cares all day and like
>> No, he's a he's a tough guy. He's not a
uh Is this it?
>> He is.
>> I think he shows up out of nowhere. I
don't know if this is the one or not,
but there's a clip where
you champ came outside with a gun. Yeah.
So, Strickland is not a guy to be
messing around with. Sure. But at the
same time, I mean, listen,
you know, comes out is, you know, it
should I hope it's a good fight. That's
the only thing. Any any of these things
that happen, you want to see a good
fight.
>> It's going to be a good fight.
>> Yeah.
>> And uh
>> I'm so excited for that fight.
>> Yeah. You're going to be there.
>> Yeah.
>> That's going to be May is going to be
where where is that fight at?
>> New Jersey.
>> New Jersey. Okay.
Got it.
>> New Jersey. And then June is going to be
Are you going to be at the White House?
Uh, we'll see. I got to talk to you. See
how maybe is, maybe no. So
>> So if you're not if you're not on the
card, are you going to go?
>> I feel you have to be there.
>> Yeah, I have I have to be there.
>> You have to cuz right away the camera is
going to go right on you.
>> Yeah, I got to I got to ask UFC and
we'll see what they
>> Oh, there is no way in the world you're
not going to be there. Like it's not
going to be them. It's going to be you
choosing to be there. They have to have
you in the arena.
>> So we'll see. They they didn't ask me
like to be there, but I'm going to ask
them let me if I'm not going to fight,
let me sit on the first row and like to
be there because it's my uh title fight.
Uh it's in my weight class. If not, I
heard they selling tickets, so I just
buy it and go. Who cares?
>> You don't need to buy it.
>> You don't need to buy it. I think Dana,
you know, whoever it is, they they
because here's what's going to happen.
Whatever ends up happening, say 9010
wins and Justin is still a dog. Like he
can make one contact and it's a
>> you never know. Can imagine you're like
underestimated
Ger and he goes and knock him out.
>> By the way, every single time he's been
in a fight. Every single time he's been
in a fight, you're like, "Wow, you know,
maybe the other guy could win it
>> even last week."
>> And he comes out of he's like, "How the
hell does he do he's an insane fighter?
He's an insane fighter who is
>> so much experience."
>> He has so much experience. Yeah. But
whatever whatever happens in the
results, the camera is gonna pan out and
it's gonna go right here.
>> Yeah.
>> So, it's gonna happen. It's gonna go
right here. And then uh
>> I'm excited. Yeah.
>> Excited.
>> I'm excited. I'm going to try to be
there as well. If you're going to go
there and they're fighting, I'm going to
try to go there as well myself. And uh
we went to this last one. Dana's u in my
opinion, he's the best promoter in the
world out of all sports. Dana is uh
>> one of a kind and we're a big fan. Arma
John, this was great. I really
appreciate you coming out. I'm glad I uh
we uh we exchanged messages and we made
it work. I know you had a fight going
on, so you did your thing and now you're
here and uh I look forward to the day we
celebrate as the first Armenian UFC
champion.
>> Yeah. So when I get the belt, I flew out
here and put the belt on this table and
we talk again
>> 100%. And then maybe we fly to Armenia
together.
>> Oh,
>> and then that's a whole different story
and we go out there and celebrate how
the
>> people going to be your favorite
favorite food. I like
>> more Armenian. Armenian
>> Armenian
>> dolma
>> dolma but it's you know remember I'm
parskah
>> so parskah for me we have this stew
called sabzi I don't know if you've had
it or not
>> have you ever gone to Rafy's place
>> yeah I've been there
>> okay so if you go to Rafy's place
>> rice with
>> with this stew that they have can you
type in hormesi
>> how he's going to
>> he try to spell it okay do g h o r m E
and then go space. There you go. Right
there. And then go to images.
I'm not even kidding you. Watching it,
I'm getting hungry.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I've tried.
>> That is the greatest meal. If I have a
last meal, they come to me. They said,
"What do you want your last meal to be?"
It's this guy right here.
>> Yeah. I've tried this.
>> My And if the people know how to make it
>> with the rice.
>> With the rice. Yeah. And maybe a little
bit of somach. I know that kind of. Now,
so now you gave me idea what I'm going
to do next for my uh fooding food in the
>> Oh, if you know how to make this.
>> No, no. I just just order and like do
food content with this food.
>> Oh, brother. I uh uh I'm willing to bet
anybody that's watching this right now
that is Armenian or Parahai or Iranian,
they're going to know about gourmets
too. This is hands down the greatest
meal in the world. You will age
backwards if you eat it from the right
person. And it's that good.
>> Yeah,
>> brother.
>> Thank you. Anytime much. I hope you I'll
see you in the
>> in Washington DC.
>> I look forward to it. If you're telling
me you're going, I look forward to it. I
I got to find a way to get out.
>> I'll I'll I'll call Donna Hunter and uh
they're going to let me be there because
>> it's it's a must
>> because I'm a favorite
fighter.
>> You're their favorite fighter. That's no
issues, no nothing. No problems with
you.
>> Good guy to deal with easiest guy to
deal with.
Never ever problem with me. So
>> now
>> no more maniac anymore.
>> No more no more no more head. Yes.
>> Can't imagine me doing something on the
White House.
>> Well, listen, you said spectacle, but
you know there's a balance to it, right?
On what happens.
>> You got to know where you where you do
in the White House. There's snipers at
the top. You got drones. You got the
president sitting there. Have you met
Have you met the president? Have you?
I've seen him but not in person.
>> You haven't met him. Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, I'm big fan of Trump, too. So,
>> there you go. You like strong
personalities, both?
>> Yes.
>> Trump Putin.
>> Take care, everybody. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
You know, this whole thing with VIN and
PBD podcast started with a phone. Me and
Mario. That's it. And it grew today to,
you know, 15 million subscribers almost
and 164 full-time employees. And that
relationship or you watching us and
supporting us wouldn't happen without
you. But did you know 51% of you that
watch the content are not subscribed to
the channel? And it would mean the world
to us if you could press that subscribe
button and notification. Why? It allows
us to grow, hire more, do bigger
interviews, have a bigger team, and
deliver a better product to you. So, if
you haven't yet, if you don't mind,
press that subscribe button. It would
mean the world to us. Thank you so much.